seoprofiler.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy policy

### The short version

Your privacy matters to us. We don't even know the password that you use to login to your SEOprofiler account because it is stored as a [salted hash value](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cryptographic_hash_function). That is why you have to reset your password if you forget it. Privacy protection is a top priority for us. Your data is safe.

This website uses cookies. A cookie is a small piece of text sent to your browser by a website you visit. It helps the website to remember information about your visit, like your preferred language and other settings. That can make your next visit easier and the site more useful to you. Cookies play an important role. Without them, using the web would be a much more frustrating experience.

* * *

### The long version

We use collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

We do not share your email address or other personally identifying information with any third parties, except our service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

Your browser installs a cookie on your computer when you visit our site. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies are required to use the SEOprofiler services. They facilitate access to our website and personalize your online experience.

In addition, our server logs automatically collect information, such as your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users' movements around our site and understand trends.

We also use standard internet tools, such as third-party analytics from Clicky, to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. We also use "Like" buttons from Facebook and other providers. Information might be send to Facebook and other providers if you load or use these buttons. Cookies can be deleted in your web browser. To delete Flash cookies, visit this [page](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/de/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

We use collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, partner program, contact, enforce our Terms of Use, and research.

We use third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run SEOprofiler. The technical processing and transmission of the Service, including your content, may involve (a) transmissions over various networks, and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices.

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure. Our servers are hosted in the USA. That means that your data will be processed in the USA.

We may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas, warrants, other valid legal processes, or when your actions violate the terms and conditions. In addition, we may disclose certain information to our service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.

We do not share your email information with third parties, except our service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

If you sign up for an account, we collect your email address. We may occasionally use this email to contact you for site-related issues. If you do not want us to contact you for commercial purposes, you can change the settings in your account. SEOprofiler complies with the Federal Can-Spam Act (15 U.S.C. 7701 et seq.).
